## CV of Elvir Misini



Name: Elvir

Surname: M<u>isini</u>

Birthday: 2000-04-26

Address: St. Dervish Hima/ 10000/Kosova, Prishtine

Email: elvirmisini@gmail.com

Driver licence: Yes

### **About Me:**

I am a hardworking and ambitious individual with a great passion for Engineering. I have excellent communication skills, enabling me to effectively communicate with a wide range of people. I am seeing a full-time position in the industry in which I can put into practice my knowledge and experience, ultimately benefiting the operations of the organisation that I work for. I have gained some good skills in University while working in different project with my teammates, and as an intern in internship programs with more advanced Restful Api projects.

### Experience:

STARLABS Python(Django) Internship February 2022 - Current

APPDEC Software Developer Internship July 2021 - November 2021

### **Education:**

- -University of Prishtina "Hasan Prishtina", Bachelor's degree, Computer Engineering (2018-2022)
- -SHML RUZHDI BERISHA, September 2015 May 2018

### Aditional Info:

- -TECHSTITUTION TRAINING February 2021 February 2021, Web development, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript and Bootstrap.
- -GitHub: https://github.com/elvirmisini
- -Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/elvir-misini-479547202/

#### Skills:

Python Django(Experienced)
Python Flask(Experienced)
PostgreSql(Experienced)
HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery, AJAX, Bootstrap(Experienced)
OOP(Experienced)
Asp.Net Core (Experienced)
MySql (Experienced)

#### Hobbies:

Boxing, Hiking, Fitness.

## Language 1

Albanian Level: Native

# Language 2

English Level: B2